history.org 2007-12-26

# Colonial Williamsburg:Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy Statement  
This is the Web site of **The Colonial Williamsburg Foundation**.  

**Postal address:  
**The Colonial Williamsburg Foundation  
P. O. Box 1776  
Williamsburg, VA 23187-1776

E-mail: [geninfo@cwf.org](mailto:geninfo@cwf.org)  
Telephone: (757) 229-1000

**Information We Collect and Store  
**For each visitor to our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). We collect domain names in order to assess aggregate information regarding pages that consumers visit. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web site and is not shared with other organizations.

**How We Use Information  
**We use pixels or transparent GIF files to help manage our online advertising. These files enable us and our advertising partner to recognize unique codes on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our Web site. The information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address.

**Personally Identifiable Information  
**The Colonial Williamsburg Foundation Web sites will only collect personal information that you knowingly and voluntarily provide when, for example, you order products or tickets, make reservations, or sign up to receive information. If you supply us with your postal or e-mail address online, you may receive periodic communications from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. 

**Children’s Online Privacy  
**We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. The only exception is our electronic field trip forum for registered schools where e-mail addresses are collected to verify registration. 

> **Offline Information:** We do not collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children. 
> 
> **Third Party Distribution:** We do not distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information from children. 
> 
> **Electronic Postcards:** Although senders must furnish an e-mail address to send electronic postcards, we do not save e-mail addresses on our servers when children send e-postcards from the “Kids Zone.” Also, these e-mail addresses are not distributed to third parties or used for any other purpose. 

**Outside Links  
**Links to other Web sites are occasionally provided as a convenience for our users and their inclusion does not imply the Foundation’s endorsement of content or responsibility for use of these sites. Please carefully read all terms and conditions of each Web site you visit. 

**How to Remove Your Information  
**If you do not wish to receive information from Colonial Williamsburg, please let us know by using the contact information above. If you are contacting us via e-mail at geninfo@cwf.org, please label the e-mail with the subject "OPT-OUT". Remember to provide us with your exact name and address so that we can remove your name from our list.

If you prefer to stop receiving unsolicited postal mailings in general, you can send your name to

Mail Preference Service  
Direct Marketing Association  
P. O. Box 9008  
Farmingdale, NY 11735-9008.

Companies that participate in this service will stop the rental of your name.

**How to Reach Us  
**For comments about this Web site contact the [Webmaster. ](mailto:mstutz@cwf.org)

For a more specific policy for williamsburgmarketplace.com, please view [www.williamsburgmarketplace.com/privacy.asp](https://www.williamsburgmarketplace.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/PrivacyPolicyView?storeId=10001&catalogId=10602&langId=-1).

This Privacy Policy was last updated January 1, 2007. Future updates to our policy will be noted here.
